

## **About Me**

I was born in 2003 in Iran. I bought my first computer when I was 8 years old. I was very interested in it and did interesting things like photo editing with it. At the age of 14, I became acquainted with programming and felt that this was what I was talented at, so I started learning Android programming only through Google and without a teacher or boot camp. After a while, I developed and published several apps. But after about two years because of more interest in JavaScript I decided to change my stack. I have been working and enjoying Front-End for about two years now.

#### **Contact**

Iran, Qom +98 922 085 2691 AhmadKarimzadeDev@gmail.com github.com/ahmadkzx ahmadkzx.github.io linkedin.com/in/ahmad-karimzade

stackoverflow.com/users/13557186

## Languages

#### Persian

0

**(1)** 

in

Native Langauge

**English** 

**Turkish** 

### **Education**

**High School Diploma, Mathematics** Andisheh High School

# **Ahmad Karimzade**

## Front-End Developer

## **Experience**

Front-End Developer | 2020/2 - 2020/8 | Qom-Iran | Full Time

at: AKWeb

Develop Wordpress Themes

Front-End Developer | 2020/8 - 2021/3 | Tehran-Iran | Full Time

at: Mizbansite www.mizbansite.com

- Develop Mizbansite main website using Wordpress
- Develop ArtArk main website using Vue

Front-End Developer | 2021/5 - 2021/9 | Toronto-Canada | Part Time

at: Ever Assistant www.everassistant.io

• Debug and improve codes

Front-End Developer | 2020/10 - Present | Qom-Iran | Full Time

at: Basalam www.basalam.com

• Develop chat section

Git

Sass

WebVitals

- Develop landings
- Develop referral games

## **Professional Skills**

HTML & CSS	Javascript	Vue / Nuxt	React / Next
Rresponsive	ES6	SSR	Compontens
Flexbox	Scopes	Vuex	Router
Variables	Asynchronous Js	Routing	Hooks
SEO	Hoisting	Lazy Load	SSR
Standards	Caching	Components	SSG
&	Service Worker	Middleweare	&
Node.js	Type Coercion	Nuxt Helpers	
Rest API Design	Closure	AsyncData / Fetch	
CRUD	Storages	Navigation Guards	
Express	Module Patterns	Transition	
Authentication	&	Plugin	
&		&	

**Bootstrap** 

**PosgreSQL** 

**NPM** 

## **Projects**

#### Official

#### ArtArk (Nuxt)

ArtArk company website, which works in the field of providing SEO services, etc

· www.artark.ir

#### Maktab Salam (Vue)

Basalam college (Maktab Salam) landing

www.maktab.basalam.com

#### Mizbansite (Wordpress)

Mizbansite site that provides hosting services

www.mizbansite.com

#### Vision Team (Vue, Nuxt)

vision marketing team website

www.vizhenteam.ir

#### iMusicPlus (Wordpress, Vue)

iMusicPlus, download music wordpress theme

· www.imusicplus.ir

#### GamePlus (Vue, Wordpress, Wocommerce)

GamePlus wordpress gaming shop theme.

www.artark.ir/demo/GamePlus

#### **AKMovie** (Wordpress)

AKMovie, download movie wordpress theme

www.artark.ir/demo/AKMovie

## **Open Source**

#### Personal Blog (React, Next)

My personal blog

www.github.com/ahmadkzx/blog

#### File Creator VSCode Extension (Node, VSCode)

Create files using templats extension

- www.marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName= AhmadKZX.file-creator
- www.github.com/ahmadkzx/vscode-file-creator

#### Trello Clone (Vue)

Trello clone project without API. using Vue and Vuex

www.github.com/ahmadkzx/trello-clone

#### **Vue Router Loading** (NPM, Vue)

Easy to use and highly customizable Vue Router Loading

- www.npmjs.com/package/vue-router-loading
- www.github.com/ahmadkzx/vue-router-loading

#### Vue Hover Zoom (NPM, Vue)

Easy to use package for zoom image when hover on it with the mouse cursor

- www.npmjs.com/package/vue-hover-zoom
- www.github.com/ahmadkzx/vue-hover-zoom

#### **H-Chat** (React, Node, Socket.io)

Simple realtime chat web app using socket

www.github.com/ahmadkzx/h-chat

#### Vue Super Console (NPM, Vue)

Beautiful floating console for Vue with features such as screenshot, copy log text and... replace of the browser console.

- www.npmjs.com/package/vue-super-console
- www.github.com/ahmadkzx/vue-super-console